(Bert:)Hear, hear.
Cheers.
(Mrs Petrescu:)Cheers. Filmed before
a live studio audience.
(Leonard:)And that is how a short
asthmatic scientist
(Leonard:)landed a stone cold fox.
(Awkward guy:)Oh. Whoa.
(Awkward guy:)I didn't know you can
propose to the same person
(Awkward guy:)so many times.
(Leonard:)The third time,
I did it in skywriting,
(Leonard:)but she never looked up.
(Penny:)You know, once,
I proposed to him.
(Leonard:)Yeah. I said no.
(Leonard:)Why?
(Leonard:)I just wanted to
make her work for it.
(Penny:)Yeah, that's gonna
cost you later.
(Red-haired guy:)Hang on. Is she just with
you because you're rich?
(Leonard:)She makes more
money than I do!
What?! Who are you?!
(Sheldon:)Do you know
what else I love about you?
(Sheldon:)Hmm?
Y-Your handwriting
is impeccable!